It's a dream, sing and smile
夢じゃん、歌い、微笑んで
I'm going to press hard, it's big
大 きく押すよ、大きい
Approximately 4 points
大 体4個分
Approximately 50,000 years in January, a little bit.
大 体1月5万万年、ちょっと、
There are more and more possibilities,
ちょっと、 どんどんに可能性が、
It seems a little close
ちょっと近いしようですよ
Everyone, if you could remove the environment that makes it easy to fight,
み なさん、戦いやすい環境を取り除いていただけたら、
That's right.
そうなんですね
Already ready, already
もう整備、もう
Why do I want to maintain it?
整 備したい なぜ
Why isn't it easy? One more battle, one more battle.
な ぜやすい ないですね もう一回 一戦 ね 一戦
one battle one battle
一 戦 一戦
One battle, one battle, one battle
一 戦 一戦 ね 一戦
Hey, why isn't there a match?
ね 一戦 なぜ ない ですね
These two are the first in Chiba.
この 2人、千葉では1つ目
From the first time
もう 1回目の方から
Eyes are also high
目 も高い
Okay, bad
よし、 やばい
Okay, bad. Okay, bad. Okay. Okay.
よし、 やばい よし、 や ばい ほ ら よし よし
Okay, now it's weird to remove this.
よし もう、これ、取り除いておかしいんだ
one more time one more time
もう 一回 もう一回
It's important, but please verify.
大 事なのに、検証してください
Although it is important, please verify it again.
大 事なのに、検証してください もう一回
one person
一 人